Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program File, 1916-2006 (Boxes 382-605)
  - 1991
    - "The Mousetrap" performance (Box-folder 540: 1)
    - Naylor, Robert W. (Box-folder 540: 2)
    - Neiman Marcus (evening at) (Box-folder 540: 3)
    - Ney, Edward (Box-folder 540: 4)
    - Nolte, Carl (Box-folder 540: 5)
    - Oakland Symphony (Box-folder 540: 6)
    - O'Connor, Sandra Day (Box-folder 540: 7)
    - Oyeda, Jaime (Box-folder 540: 8)
    - Padwe, Gerald (Box-folder 540: 9)
    - Parker, Sharon (Box-folder 540: 10)
    - Pastreich, Peter (Box-folder 540: 11)
    - Penhoet, Edward (Box-folder 540: 12)
    - Persian Gulf panel (Box-folder 540: 13)
    - Pishev, Ognian (Box-folder 540: 14)
    - Pizzo, Stephen P. (Box-folder 540: 15)
    - Plimpton, George (Box-folder 540: 16)
    - Potter, William C. (Box-folder 540: 17)
    - Press panel (Box-folder 540: 18)
    - Proposition W debate (Box-folder 540: 19)
    - Raisian, John (Box-folder 540: 20)
    - Ratto's opera night (Box-folder 540: 21)
    - Redford, Robert (Box-folder 540: 22)
    - El Reedy, El Sayed Abdel Raouf (Box-folder 540: 23)
    - Regional Center for the Arts (Box-folder 540: 24)
    - Rhodes, Frank H. T. (Box-folder 540: 25)
    - Rice, Condoleezza (Box-folder 540: 26)
    - Ridgway, Rosanne (Box-folder 540: 27)
    - Robinson, Mary (Box-folder 540: 28)
    - Rockefeller, John D. (Box-folder 540: 29)
    - Rogge, Peter (Box-folder 540: 30)
    - Rolley, Lynne (Box-folder 540: 31)
    - Roper, Burns W. (Box-folder 540: 32)
    - Rosenthal, James D. (Box-folder 540: 33)
    - Ross, Scott (Box-folder 541: 1)
    - Ruckelshaus, William (Box-folder 541: 2)
    - Rund, Charles (Box-folder 541: 3)
    - Al-Sabah, Ali al Khalifa (Box-folder 541: 4)
    - Sachs, Jeffrey (Box-folder 541: 5)
    - Salinas de Gortari, Carlos (Box-folder 541: 5)
    - Sanford, Bruce W. (Box-folder 541: 7)
    - San Francisco Girls Chorus Virtuosi (Box-folder 541: 8)
    - San Jose Airport (Box-folder 541: 9)
    - Santa Clara Theater Program (Box-folder 541: 10)
    - Sawhill, John C. (Box-folder 541: 11)
    - Schroeder, Patricia (Box-folder 541: 12)
    - Schweitzer, Robert (Box-folder 541: 13)
    - Schuler, Henry M. (Box-folder 541: 14)
    - Schwartz, Peter (Box-folder 541: 15)
    - Schwarzkopf, Norman H. (Box-folder 541: 16)
    - Serfling, Aubrey (Box-folder 541: 17)
    - Seymour, John (Box-folder 541: 18)
    - Shaw, Bernard (Box-folder 541: 19)
    - Sher, Byron (Box-folder 541: 20)
    - Sikes, Alfred C. (Box-folder 541: 21)
    - Silaev, Ivan S. (Box-folder 541: 22)
    - Silbert, Mimi (Box-folder 541: 23)
    - Simon, Julian L. (Box-folder 541: 24)
    - Singer, Maxine F. (Box-folder 542: 1)
    - Smith, Geoffrey (Box-folder 542: 2)
    - Smith, Mike (Box-folder 542: 3)
    - Solarz, Stephen J. (Box-folder 542: 4)
    - Solomon, Norman (Box-folder 542: 5)
    - Speier, Jackie (Box-folder 542: 6)
    - Sports Illustrated panel of editors (Box-folder 542: 7)
    - Stempel, Robert (Box-folder 542: 8)
    - Stolberg, Ted (Box-folder 542: 9)
    - Strand, David (Box-folder 542: 10)
    - Sullivan, Louis W. (Box-folder 542: 11)
    - Tabatabai, Zohren (Box-folder 542: 12)
    - Tickell, Crispin (Box-folder 542: 13)
    - Tien, Chang-lin (Box-folder 542: 14)
    - Toffler, Alvin (Box-folder 542: 15)
    - Toomey, Bill (Box-folder 542: 16)
    - Townes, Charles (Box-folder 542: 17)
    - Townley, Preston (Box-folder 542: 18)
    - Transportation panel (Box-folder 542: 19)
    - Tunney, Jim (Box-folder 542: 20)
    - U.S. Windpower tour (Box-folder 542: 21)
    - Vasconcellos, John (Box-folder 542: 22)
    - Walter, J. Jackson (Box-folder 542: 23)
    - Waterman, Bob (Box-folder 542: 24)
    - Wente, Carolyn (Box-folder 542: 25)
    - Wertheimer, Fred (Box-folder 542: 26)
    - Westheimer, Ruth (Box-folder 542: 27)
    - Wiley, Peter Booth (Box-folder 542: 28)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 542: 29)
    - Wine tasting (Box-folder 543: 1)
    - Wirth, Timothy B. (Box-folder 543: 2-3)
    - Women in media panel (Box-folder 543: 4)
    - Woolley, Persia (Box-folder 543: 5-6)
    - Yeutter, Clayton (Box-folder 543: 7)
    - Zinchuk, Alexander (Box-folder 543: 8)
    - Zinner, Paul (Box-folder 543: 9)
  - 1992
    - AIDS panel (Box-folder 543: 10)
    - Alioto, Angela (Box-folder 543: 11)
    - Alpher, Joseph (Box-folder 543: 12)
    - Anderson, John (Box-folder 543: 13)
    - Armacost, Michael (Box-folder 543: 14)
    - Artistic Directors/Theatre (Box-folder 543: 15)
    - Arts in Transition/Challenges for the Theater in the 1990s (ballet, opera, symphony, theater) (Box-folder 543: 16)
    - Baker, William P. (Box-folder 543: 17)
    - Banac, Ivo (Box-folder 543: 18)
    - Barlett, Donald L., and James B. Steele (Box-folder 543: 19)
    - Barr, William P. (Box-folder 543: 20)
    - Beer tasting (Box-folder 543: 21)
    - Belkhayat, Mohamed (Box-folder 543: 22)
    - Benhan, Jim (Box-folder 543: 23)
    - Benito, Carlos, and David McNamara (Box-folder 543: 24)
    - Bienen, Henry S. (Box-folder 543: 25)
    - Bildt, Carl (Box-folder 543: 26)
    - Biotech panel (Box-folder 543: 27)
    - Black, Shirley Temple (Box-folder 543: 28)
    - Blackmun, Harry A. (Box-folder 543: 29)
    - Borchegrave, Arnaud de (Box-folder 543: 30)
    - Bortz, Walter M. (Box-folder 544: 1)
    - Bradley, Bill (Box-folder 544: 2)
    - Breast cancer panel (Box-folder 544: 3)
    - Bryan, Robert R. (Box-folder 544: 4)
    - Buchanan, Pat (Box-folder 544: 5)
    - Buckeye Roadhouse (Box-folder 544: 6)
    - Bullin, Christine (Box-folder 544: 7)
    - Callan, Dawn (Box-folder 544: 8)
    - Card, Andrew H. (Box-folder 544: 9)
    - Casey, Ginger (Box-folder 544: 10)
    - Catto, Henry E. (Box-folder 544: 11)
    - Christmas concert (Box-folder 544: 12)
    - Clarke, Richard A. (Box-folder 544: 13)
    - Clorox tour (Box-folder 544: 14)
    - Congressional district debate (Box-folder 544: 15-16)
    - Corlin, Richard F. (Box-folder 544: 17)
    - Cristiani, Alfredo (Box-folder 544: 18)
    - Dart, Iris Rainer (Box-folder 544: 19)
    - Davidow, William H. (Box-folder 544: 20-21)
    - Dellums, Ron (Box-folder 544: 22)
    - Dement, William C. (Box-folder 544: 23)
    - Dershowitz, Alan (Box-folder 544: 24)
    - Djerassi, Carl (Box-folder 544: 25)
    - Edelin, Kenneth C. (Box-folder 544: 26)
    - Edelman, Marian Wright (Box-folder 545: 1)
    - Elias, Jorge Serrano (Box-folder 545: 2)
    - Ellis, Alan, and Michael Rushford (Box-folder 545: 3)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 545: 4)
    - European journalists panel (Box-folder 545: 5)
    - Evans, Gareth (Box-folder 545: 6)
    - Feinstein, Dianne, and John Seymour debate (Box-folder 545: 7)
    - Ferris, Timothy (Box-folder 545: 8)
    - Field, Mervin (Box-folder 545: 9)
    - Filante, Bill (Box-folder 545: 10)
    - Firebombers (Box-folder 545: 11)
    - Folberg, Jay (Box-folder 545: 12)
    - Forbes, Malcolm (Box-folder 545: 13)
    - Foster, Judie (Box-folder 545: 14)
    - Franklin, Barbara H. (Box-folder 545: 15)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 545: 16-17)
    - Garamendi, John (Box-folder 545: 18)
    - Gardner, Robert K. (Box-folder 545: 19)
    - Garment, Suzanne (Box-folder 545: 20)
    - Garzarelli, Elaine M. (Box-folder 545: 21)
    - Gaviria, Cesar (Box-folder 545: 22)
    - Germania Restaurant (Box-folder 545: 23)
    - Gershwin pops concert (Box-folder 545: 24)
    - Getty, Gordon P. (Box-folder 545: 25)
    - Gingerbread House dinner (Box-folder 545: 26)
    - Ginn, Sam (Box-folder 545: 27)
    - Goldman, Richard (Box-folder 546: 1)
    - Gomis, Charles (Box-folder 546: 2)
    - Göncz, Árpád (Box-folder 546: 3)
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail (Box-folder 546: 4)
    - Gorbunovs, Anatolijs (Box-folder 546: 5)
    - Gramm, Phil (Box-folder 546: 6)
    - Grechko, Georgy (Box-folder 546: 7)
    - Green, Lucille (Box-folder 546: 8)
    - Greider, William (Box-folder 546: 9)
    - Haas, Richard (Box-folder 546: 10)
    - Harkin, Tom (Box-folder 546: 11)
    - Harris, Elihu (Box-folder 546: 12)
    - Harris, Louis (Box-folder 546: 13)
    - Hart, Mickey (Box-folder 546: 14)
    - Headlands Center (Box-folder 546: 15)
    - Health care panel (Box-folder 546: 16)
    - Heller, Robert (Box-folder 546: 17)
    - Hepburn, Audrey (Box-folder 546: 18)
    - Herrington, Lois (Box-folder 546: 19)
    - Herschensohn, Bruce (Box-folder 546: 20)
    - Heydorn, William H. (Box-folder 546: 21)
    - Hoadley, Walter (Box-folder 546: 22)
    - Holiday music program (Box-folder 547: 1)
    - Houck, John W. (Box-folder 547: 2)
    - Hume, Brit (Box-folder 547: 3)
    - Humphry, Derek M. (Box-folder 547: 4)
    - Inouye, Daniel K. (Box-folder 547: 5)
    - Isaacson, Walter (Box-folder 547: 6)
    - Johansen, Gary (Box-folder 547: 7)
    - Johnson, Walter (Box-folder 547: 8)
    - Jordan, Frank (Box-folder 547: 9)
    - Jorgensen, Jim (Box-folder 547: 10)
    - Josephson, Michael (Box-folder 547: 11)
    - Kabul (Special event) (Box-folder 547: 12)
    - Kaplan, Justin (Box-folder 547: 13)
    - Karamanlis, Constantine (Box-folder 547: 14)
    - Kaschak, Ellyn, and Terry Kupers (Box-folder 547: 15)
    - Katchadourian, Herant (Box-folder 547: 16)
    - Keen, Sam (Box-folder 547: 17)
    - Kennedy, David M. (Box-folder 547: 18)
    - Kerrey, Bob (Box-folder 547: 19)
    - Klingenstein, Paul, and Jim Shapiro (Box-folder 547: 20)
    - Kney-Tal, Harry (Box-folder 547: 21)
    - Kozberg, Joanne Corday (Box-folder 547: 22)
    - Kuntz, Robert (Box-folder 547: 23)
    - Kuriyama, Tarakaz U. (Box-folder 547: 24)
    - Laffer, Arthur (Box-folder 547: 25)
    - Lafontaine, Oscar (Box-folder 547: 26)
    - Lafontant-Mankarious, Jewel (Box-folder 547: 27)
    - Lando, John, and Grant Welling (Box-folder 547: 28)
    - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory (Box-folder 548: 1)
    - Leno, Jay (Box-folder 548: 2)
    - Lerner, Michael (Box-folder 548: 3)
    - Lessig, Paul, and James Whittaker (Box-folder 548: 4)
    - Linowitz, Sol (Box-folder 548: 5)
    - Lipinski, Andrew J. (Box-folder 548: 6)
    - Lovins, Amory (Box-folder 548: 7)
    - Ludmer, Paul (with Michael Lee and Robert Feldman) (Box-folder 548: 8)
    - Lungren, Daniel E. (Box-folder 548: 9)
    - McCain, John (Box-folder 548: 10)
    - McCullough, David (Box-folder 548: 11)
    - McGovern, George (Box-folder 548: 12)
    - McKenna, Regis (Box-folder 548: 13)
    - McLean, Denis B. G. (Box-folder 548: 14)
    - McLellan, Rod (Box-folder 548: 15)
    - McNamara, Joseph D. (Box-folder 548: 16)
    - Macnee, Patrick (Box-folder 548: 17)
    - Madrid Hurtado, Miguel de la (Box-folder 548: 18)
    - Magaw, John W. (Box-folder 548: 19)
    - Magic show (Box-folder 548: 20)
    - Maksoud, Clovis (Box-folder 548: 21)
    - Malcolm, Ellen (Box-folder 549: 1)
    - Malden, Karl (Box-folder 549: 2)
    - Marine Science Institute (Box-folder 549: 3)
    - Marion, John L. (Box-folder 549: 4)
    - Maynard, Robert C. (Box-folder 549: 5)
    - Mazzuca, Kim M. (Box-folder 549: 6)
    - Meese, Edwin (Box-folder 549: 7)
    - Michelman, Kate (Box-folder 549: 8)
    - Miller, George (Box-folder 549: 9)
    - Mirassou dinner (Box-folder 549: 10)
    - Moffett Field (Box-folder 549: 11)
    - Monterey Bay Aquarium (Box-folder 549: 12)
    - Mudd, Roger (Box-folder 549: 13)
    - Mueller, Nancy (Box-folder 549: 14)
    - Mulroney, Brian (Box-folder 549: 15)
    - Murphy, Michael (Box-folder 549: 16)
    - NASA tour (Box-folder 549: 17)
    - Nathan's Restaurant (Box-folder 549: 18)
    - Nicholas, Janet (Box-folder 549: 19)
    - Novello, Antonia (Box-folder 549: 20)
    - Nunn, Sam (Box-folder 549: 21)
    - O'Keefe, Sean (Box-folder 549: 22)
    - O'Neill, Brian (Box-folder 549: 23)
    - O'Rourke, P. J. (Box-folder 549: 24)
    - Palter, Louis (Box-folder 549: 25)
    - Parker, Sharon (Box-folder 549: 26)
    - Parry, Robert (Box-folder 549: 27)
    - Pei, I. M. (Box-folder 549: 28)
    - Pepper, Linda (Box-folder 549: 29)
    - Philippines panel (Box-folder 549: 30)
    - Picasso, Paloma (Box-folder 549: 31)
    - Pipes, Richard (Box-folder 549: 32)
    - Pritikin, Robert (Box-folder 549: 33)
    - Qizhen, Zhu (Box-folder 550: 1)
    - Raisian, John (Box-folder : 2)
    - Randall, Tony (Box-folder 550: 3)
    - Rappaport, Andrew S. (Box-folder 550: 4)
    - Ratto's operatic evening (Box-folder 550: 5)
    - Rawls, Jim (Box-folder 550: 6)
    - Reilly, Mary Morgan (Box-folder 550: 7)
    - Reilly, William K. (Box-folder 550: 8)
    - Renwick, Robin (Box-folder 550: 9)
    - Reynolds, Albert (Box-folder 550: 10)
    - Rice, Condoleezza (Box-folder 550: 11)
    - Riggs, Frank (Box-folder 550: 12)
    - Rogge, Peter (Box-folder 550: 13)
    - Roper, William L. (Box-folder 550: 14)
    - Ryan, Timothy (Box-folder 550: 15)
    - Sake tasting (Box-folder 550: 16)
    - Salisbury, Harrison (Box-folder 550: 17)
    - Scheuftan, Dan (Box-folder 550: 18)
    - Schmidt, Beno (Box-folder 550: 19)
    - Schmitter, Philippe C. (Box-folder 550: 20)
    - Schorr, Lisbeth B. (Box-folder 550: 21)
    - Schrage, Michael (Box-folder 550: 22)
    - Seventh Assembly seat debate (Box-folder 550: 23)
    - Shostak, Seth (Box-folder 550: 24)
    - Shoval, Zalman (Box-folder 551: 1)
    - Silicon Valley Capital Club (Box-folder 551: 2)
    - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center tour (Box-folder 551: 3)
    - Statham, Stan (Box-folder 551: 4)
    - Steel, Jon (Box-folder 551: 5)
    - Stewart, James B. (Box-folder 551: 6)
    - Stockdale, James (Box-folder 551: 7)
    - Stoddard, Alexandra (Box-folder 551: 8)
    - Svanevik, Michael (Box-folder 551: 9)
    - Swenson, Larry, and Mike Humphrey (Box-folder 551: 10)
    - Swig, Charlotte and Mel (Box-folder 551: 11)
    - Sybert, Richard (Box-folder 551: 12)
    - Syme, Leonard (Box-folder 551: 13)
    - Tabone, Censu (Box-folder 551: 14)
    - Tague, Kristin (Box-folder 551: 15)
    - Tannen, Deborah (Box-folder 551: 16)
    - Taylor, Hunt (Box-folder 551: 17)
    - Thompson, Mark (Box-folder 551: 18)
    - Tien, Chang-lin (Box-folder 551: 19)
    - Timberman, David (Box-folder 551: 20)
    - Triant, Deborah (Box-folder 551: 21)
    - Trillin, Calvin Marshall (Box-folder 551: 22)
    - Usery, William J. (Box-folder 551: 23)
    - USS Abraham Lincoln tour (Box-folder 551: 24)
    - Valenti, Jack (Box-folder 551: 25)
    - Vartanian, Elsie (Box-folder 551: 26)
    - Vasquez, Daniel (Box-folder 551: 27)
    - Waters, Maxine (Box-folder 551: 28)
    - Watkins, James D. (Box-folder 551: 29)
    - Werne, Roger W. (Box-folder 551: 30)
    - West, Cornell (Box-folder 551: 31)
    - West Bay Opera (Box-folder 551: 32)
    - Wildansky, Aaron (Box-folder 551: 33)
    - Wilson's Welfare (Box-folder 551: 34)
    - Wine tasting (Box-folder 551: 35)
    - "Witness for the Prosecution" (Box-folder 551: 36)
    - Wolf, Naomi (Box-folder 551: 37)
    - Wollin, Gary (Box-folder 552: 1)
    - Wriston, Walter B. (Box-folder 552: 2)
  - 1993
    - Albright, Madeleine Korbel (Box-folder 552: 3)
    - Allen, Graham (Box-folder 552: 4)
    - Amelio, Gilbert F. (Box-folder 552: 5)
    - Anderson, Terry (Box-folder 552: 6)
    - Andréani, Jacques (Box-folder 552: 7)
    - Annenberg, Walter (Box-folder 552: 8)
    - Annual Holiday concert (Box-folder 552: 9)
    - Appel, Edward (Box-folder 552: 10)
    - Arafat, Yasir (Box-folder 552: 11)
    - Ashe, Arthur (Box-folder 552: 12)
    - Aspin, Les (Box-folder 552: 13)
    - Attles, Al (Box-folder 552: 14)
    - Audubon Canyon Ranch (Box-folder 552: 15)
    - Bajarin, Tim (Box-folder 552: 16)
    - Baker, Bill (Box-folder 552: 17)
    - Baldridge, Leticia (Box-folder 552: 18)
    - Barbach, Lonnie, and David Geisinger (Box-folder 552: 19)
    - Barrales, Ruben (Box-folder 552: 20)
    - Barry, Dave (Box-folder 552: 21)
    - Bennett, William J. (Box-folder 552: 22)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd M. (Box-folder 552: 23)
    - Bieber, Owen (Box-folder 552: 24)
    - Biya, Paul (Box-folder 552: 25)
    - Black, Cathleen (Box-folder 552: 26)
    - Blanchard, Richard A. (Box-folder 552: 27)
    - "Blue Cube" tour (Box-folder 552: 28)
    - "Bohème, La" (performance) (Box-folder 553: 1)
    - Boren, David (Box-folder 553: 2)
    - Bozeman, Todd (Box-folder 553: 3)
    - Bradley, Tom (Box-folder 553: 4)
    - Brande, Luc Van Den (Box-folder 553: 5)
    - Brown, Delmer (Box-folder 553: 6)
    - Buffett, Warren (Box-folder 553: 7)
    - Bundschuh, George A. W. (Box-folder 553: 8)
    - Burch, Laurel (Box-folder 553: 9)
    - Cain, Becky (Box-folder 553: 10)
    - California State University (Hayward) faculty panel (Box-folder 553: 11)
    - Campbell, Martha (Box-folder 553: 12)
    - Carranza, Julio (Box-folder 553: 13)
    - Carville, James (Box-folder 553: 14)
    - Cato Institution (Box-folder 553: 15)
    - Chavis, Benjamin (Box-folder 553: 16)
    - Chomsky, Noam (Box-folder 553: 17)
    - Choppin, Purnell (Box-folder 553: 18)
    - Christman, Steve B. (Box-folder 553: 19)
    - Christopher, Warren (Box-folder 553: 20)
    - Clark, Jim (Box-folder 553: 21)
    - Colby, William E. (Box-folder 553: 22)
    - Conlin, William P. (Box-folder 553: 23)
    - Connor, Linda (Box-folder 553: 24)
    - Cooke, Alistair (Box-folder 553: 25)
    - Country western BBQ and line dancing (Box-folder 553: 26)
    - Cromwell, Brian (Box-folder 553: 27)
    - Crowe, William J. (Box-folder 553: 28)
    - Dahlin, Douglas P. (Box-folder 554: 1)
    - Danforth, John (Box-folder 554: 2)
    - Dean, Howard (Box-folder 554: 3)
    - Decorators' Showhouse at Villa Mountford (Box-folder 554: 4)
    - Defense Language Institute (Box-folder 554: 5)
    - Dellums, Ron (Box-folder 554: 6)
    - Draper, William H. (Box-folder 554: 7)
    - Drummond, William J. (Box-folder 554: 8)
    - Duesberg, Peter (Box-folder 554: 9)
    - Dunsmuir House (Box-folder 554: 10)
    - Du Pont, Pierre S. (Box-folder 554: 11)
    - Eban, Abba (Box-folder 554: 12)
    - Ebert, Roger (Box-folder 554: 13)
    - Eisner, Michael (Box-folder 554: 14)
    - Engstrom, Mats (Box-folder 554: 15)
    - Enthoven, Alain C. (Box-folder 554: 16)
    - Espy, Michael (Box-folder 554: 17)
    - Etzioni, Amitai (Box-folder 554: 18)
    - Falco, Mathea (Box-folder 554: 19)
    - Faludi, Susan (Box-folder 554: 20)
    - Farrell, Mary (Box-folder 554: 21)
    - Fouke, Bruce (Box-folder 554: 22)
    - Freeh, Louis (Box-folder 554: 23)
    - Garrison, James A. (Box-folder 554: 24-25)
    - Gates, William (Box-folder 554: 26)
    - Gay, Peter (Box-folder 554: 27)
    - Gebbie, Kristine (Box-folder 555: 1)
    - Getty, Gordon (Box-folder 555: 2-3)
    - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader (Box-folder 555: 4)
    - Giudi, Ronn (Box-folder 555: 5)
    - Giuliani, Rudolph (Box-folder 555: 6)
    - Glover, Danny (Box-folder 555: 7)
    - Goizueta, Robert (Box-folder 555: 8)
    - Gore, Tipper (Box-folder 555: 9)
    - Grace, Peter (Box-folder 555: 10)
    - Graham, Billy (Box-folder 555: 11)
    - Graves, Howard Dwayne (Box-folder 555: 12)
    - Gregory, Bettina (Box-folder 555: 13)
    - Gresser, Julian (Box-folder 555: 14)
    - Grove, Andrew S. (Box-folder 555: 15)
    - Guccione, Bob (Box-folder 555: 16)
    - Halberstam, David (Box-folder 555: 17)
    - Hallett, Carol (Box-folder 555: 18)
    - Hamburg, Dan (Box-folder 555: 19)
    - Hamlisch, Marvin (Box-folder 555: 20)
    - Hammarstrom, Peter (Box-folder 555: 21)
    - Harriman, Pamela (Box-folder 555: 22)
    - Hayes, Thomas C. (Box-folder 555: 23)
    - Health care panel (Box-folder 555: 24)
    - Henri, Crown Prince of Luxembourg (Box-folder 555: 25)
    - Hentoff, Nat (Box-folder 555: 26)
    - Hill, Charles (Box-folder 555: 27)
    - Hoadley, Walter (Box-folder 555: 28)
    - Hoffman, Elliot, and Mitchell Rofsky (Box-folder 555: 29)
    - Hollings, Earnest F. (Box-folder 555: 30)
    - Hollingsworth, Hilda (Box-folder 556: 1)
    - Holmes, Genta (Box-folder 556: 2)
    - Hoving, Thomas (Box-folder 556: 3)
    - Hutchison, Claude (Box-folder 556: 4)
    - "Inspecting Carol" (Marin Theatre Company) (Box-folder 556: 5)
    - Ivins, Molly (Box-folder 556: 6)
    - Jackson, Jesse (Box-folder 556: 7)
    - Jacobowitz, Ruth S. (Box-folder 556: 8)
    - Jasinowski, Jerry J. (Box-folder 556: 9)
    - Jawara, Dawda (Box-folder 556: 10)
    - Jenkins, Brian Michael (Box-folder 556: 11)
    - Johnson, Andrew R. (Box-folder 556: 12)
    - Johnson, Magic (Box-folder 556: 13)
    - Johnson, Philip (Box-folder 556: 14)
    - Johnson, Tom (Box-folder 556: 15)
    - Juran, Joseph (Box-folder 556: 16)
    - Kane, Robert (Box-folder 556: 17)
    - Kaplan, Justin (Box-folder 556: 18)
    - Kaufman, Phil (Box-folder 556: 19)
    - Kempton, Murray (Box-folder 556: 20)
    - Kennedy, David Michael (Box-folder 556: 21)
    - Kerry, John F. (Box-folder 556: 22)
    - King, Joseph (Box-folder 556: 23)
    - Klop, Kenneth (Box-folder 556: 24)
    - Kmiec, Douglas W. (Box-folder 556: 25)
    - Kney-Tal, Harry (Box-folder 556: 26)
    - Knight, Phil (Box-folder 556: 27)
    - Kopp, Quentin (Box-folder 556: 28)
    - Kramer, Peter D. (Box-folder 557: 1)
    - Krens, Thomas (Box-folder 557: 2)
    - Krulak, Charles (Box-folder 557: 3)
    - Kurtz, Larry (Box-folder 557: 4)
    - Lamb, David (Box-folder 557: 5)
    - Lansbury, Angela (Box-folder 557: 6)
    - Lantos, Tom (Box-folder 557: 7)
    - Lauren, Ralph (Box-folder 557: 8)
    - Lehner, Urban (Box-folder 557: 9)
    - Lewis, Jerry (Box-folder 557: 10)
    - Linnon, John (Box-folder 557: 11)
    - Loben, James W. von (Box-folder 557: 12)
    - Loewy, Erich (Box-folder 557: 13)
    - Long, Bonnie (Box-folder 557: 14)
    - Los Gatos Brewing Co. (Box-folder 557: 15)
    - Lucas, John (Box-folder 557: 16)
    - McCaw, Craig (Box-folder 557: 17)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. (Box-folder 557: 18)
    - McNamara, Joseph (Box-folder 557: 19)
    - Magaziner, Ira (Box-folder 557: 20)
    - Magic show (Box-folder 557: 21)
    - Marin Headlands walk (Box-folder 557: 22)
    - Marker, Rita (Box-folder 557: 23)
    - Martin, Fred, and Walter Johnson (Box-folder 557: 24)
    - Martin, Lynn (Box-folder 557: 25)
    - Mas, George L. (Box-folder 557: 26)
    - Matsui, Robert (Box-folder 557: 27)
    - Meese, Edwin (Box-folder 557: 28)
    - Michel, Robert H. (Box-folder 557: 29)
    - Middleton, Peter (Box-folder 557: 30)
    - Miller, Arthur T. (Box-folder 557: 31)
    - Millstein, David J. (Box-folder 557: 32)
    - Mitchell, George (Box-folder 557: 33)
    - Mitford, Jessica (Box-folder 558: 1)
    - Moe, Terry (Box-folder 558: 2)
    - Morita, Akio (Box-folder 558: 3)
    - Morrison, Tony (Box-folder 558: 4)
    - Moynihan, Daniel (Box-folder 558: 5)
    - Multimedia panel (Box-folder 558: 6)
    - Mystery dinner at Macy's Tea Room (Box-folder 558: 7)
    - Mystery writers panel (Box-folder 558: 8)
    - Nader, Ralph (Box-folder 558: 9)
    - Netanyahu, Benjamin (Box-folder 558: 10)
    - Noor, Queen, consort of Hussein, King of Jordan (Box-folder 558: 11)
    - Okun, Herbert S. (Box-folder 558: 12)
    - Paeman, Hugo (Box-folder 558: 13)
    - Panetta, Leon E. (Box-folder 558: 14)
    - Panic, Milan (Box-folder 558: 15)
    - Peltason, Jack (Box-folder 558: 16)
    - Pena, Frederico (Box-folder 558: 17)
    - Perot, Ross (Box-folder 558: 18)
    - Perry, Mark (Box-folder 558: 19)
    - Personal communicators panel (Box-folder 558: 20)
    - Petera, Tom (Box-folder 558: 21)
    - Pickens, Boone (Box-folder 559: 1)
    - Pinebrook Inn dinner (Box-folder 559: 2)
    - Poinar, George O. (Box-folder 559: 3)
    - Post, Rollin (Box-folder 559: 4)
    - Pozner, Vladimir (Box-folder 559: 5)
    - Quindlen, Anna (Box-folder 559: 6)
    - Raab, Kirk (Box-folder 559: 7)
    - Rabin, Yitzhak (Box-folder 559: 8)
    - Ramos, Fidel (Box-folder 559: 9)
    - Ray, Dixy Lee (Box-folder 559: 10)
    - Ray, Siddhartha Shankar (Box-folder 559: 11)
    - Reeves, Richard (Box-folder 559: 12)
    - Revenko, V. J. (Box-folder 559: 13)
    - Riordan, Richard (Box-folder 559: 14)
    - Ristow, John (Box-folder 559: 15)